totallifeguru.com 2018-08-17

# Privacy Policy

TotalLifeGuru.com (hereafter “TotalLifeGuru.com”,”Website”, “Site”) is dedicated to safeguarding and preserving your privacy when visiting the Website or communicating electronically with us. This Privacy Policy, together with our [Terms of Use](http://totallifeguru.com/terms-of-use/), provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you. We do update this Privacy Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly. Please note this Website is not designed for persons under the age of thirteen (13). If you are below this age, you may not use the Website.

## Information We Collect

1. Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.

2. Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website, such as when you submit a question to be answered by a professional.

3. Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

4. Use of Cookies

5. On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers.

6. Such information will not identify you personally it is aggregated statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

7. We may also place a pixel on pages on our Website, or those of our advertisers and partners. This enables us to record in our server logs that a specific user ID has visited a particular page. This data allows us to analyse and determine our audience’s behavioural characteristics, which helps us to optimise our site, advertisement placement, and marketing focus.

Similarly to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you.

All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.

Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

## Use Of Your Information

We ask for and use your personal information on the Website in order to operate, enhance and provide to you the information services you request. We (and, if appropriate, our advertising partners) may also use your personal information (utilising any of the means of contact you have provided) to provide you with information about other products, programs or services we believe may be of interest to you provided you have consented to being contacted in this way. We have put in place various security measures in accordance with industry standards to protect the security of your personal information both online and offline. may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. When you submit your personal information on the Website, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of such information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

TotalLifeGuru.com may disclose your personal information: (a) to its third party advertising partners and affiliated companies for the purpose of providing the content to you in an efficient manner; and (b) for the purpose of properly administering your account in accordance with the standard operating procedures of TotalLifeGuru.com and its partners and affiliated companies. We are not responsible for the actions of such third party companies, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to these or to any other third parties.

In addition, TotalLifeGuru.com may retain other third party vendors, consultants and other service providers to perform functions in connection with the operation of the Website on our behalf consistent with our Privacy Policy. Such third parties may be provided with access to personal information necessary to perform their functions.

In addition, TotalLifeGuru.com may disclose personal information when we are lawfully authorized or required to do so.

Information about our users, including personal information, may also be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership or in any other situation where personal information may be transferred as one of the business assets of TotalLifeGuru.com.

## Storing Your Personal Data

We may transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the United States or European Economic Area for processing and storing. Also, it may be processed by staff operating outside the United States or European Economic Area who work for us or for one of our suppliers. For example, such staff maybe engaged in the processing and concluding of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all reasonable steps to make sure that your data is treated securely and in agreement with this Privacy Policy.

Data that is provided to us is stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into on our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety. The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties where we are legally required to disclose your information.

We have put in place various security measures in accordance with industry standards to protect the security of your personal information both online and offline.

## Third Party Advertisements

TotalLifeGuru.com may also use third parties to serve ads on the Website. These third parties may collect information about your visits to this and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our Website (but not personal information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number). They do this using their own cookies, clear gifs or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Website and the other sites tracked by these third parties.  This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear gifs in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology.

We participate in affiliate marketing and allow affiliate links to be encoded on some of our pages. This means that we may earn a commission when you click on or make purchases via affiliate links and affiliate partners may use cookies to understand your use of TotalLifeGuru.com.

## Third Party Links

You may find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

## Contacting Us

We welcome any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us at [quickmoneyanswers.com@gmail.com](mailto:quickmoneyanswers.com@gmail.com).
